export const Data=[{
question:"Which HTML tag is used to create a hyperlink?",
options:["<link>","<href>"," <a>","<hyperlink>"],
answer:3
}
,{
    question: "Which of the following is not a web component element?",
    options: ["<shadow>", "<menu>", "<content>", "<element>"],
    answer: 2
},{
    question: "Which of the following programming languages is commonly used for server-side scripting in web development?",
    options: ["HTML", "CSS", "JavaScript", "PHP"],
    answer: 4
},{
    question: "Which of the following is used to read an HTML page and render it?",
    options: ["Web server", "Web matrix", "Web browser", "None of the mentioned"],
    answer: 3
},{
    question: "Which of the following is a popular front-end framework for building user interfaces in JavaScript?",
    options: ["Django", "Angular", "Flask", "Node.js"],
    answer: 2
},{
    question: "What application can one create even before the introduction of HTML5?",
    options: ["Forms", "Browser based games", "Web applications", "Mobile applications"],
    answer: 3
},{
    question: "Which of the following is not associated with web socket communication?",
    options: ["https", "wss", "http", "ws"],
    answer: 1
},{
    question: "Why are images often used on the webpage?",
    options: ["To create graphical buttons or links to other pages", "To help the webpage load efficiently", "Webpage cannot run/be displayed without at least one image", "Because webpage doesnâ€™t support pure text"],
    answer: 1
},{
    question: "What is DOM?",
    options: ["Application programming interface", "Hierarchy of objects in ASP.NET", "Convention for representing and interacting with objects in HTML documents", "None of the mentioned"],
    answer: 3
},{
    question: "What are tables in web programming?",
    options: ["Display information which are already accessed by the user", "Containing more number of rows than columns", "To only store data to be accessed later by the user", "Display information in rows and columns used to display all manner of data that fits in a grid"],
    answer: 4
},{
    question: "What does <td> stand for?",
    options: ["Table database", "Table data", "Table directory", "Table direct row"],
    answer: 2
},{
    question: "Which element is used to give title to a table?",
    options: ["Caption", "Headline", "Title", "Heading"],
    answer: 1
},{
    question: "What are forms in web programming?",
    options: ["They are matrices on web page", "They are used to create table data and its information", "They allow you to enter data which can be processed to servers", "They are the information filled by the server-side"],
    answer: 3
},
]